southeastasia.org 2011-05-30

# Privacy Policy - Southeast Asia

SoutheastAsia.org is committed to protecting the personal information that you provide to us through our web site located at www.SoutheastAsia.org (the “Site”).  We believe it is important for you to know how we protect your personal information to deliver you the best user experience possible.  This Privacy Policy covers what information is collected, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom such information is disclosed, and what precautions are taken by SoutheastAsia.org to safeguard your privacy and personal information.

This privacy policy pertains to information that is collected online, unless otherwise noted herein.  BY USING THE SITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND TO OUR PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR THE PURPOSES STATED BELOW.  IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE.

The Site contains links to other web sites.  Once you enter another web site (whether through an advertisement, service, or content link), be aware that SoutheastAsia.org is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites.  We encourage you to look for and review the privacy statements of each and every web site you visit through a link or advertisement on the Site.  

Information We Collect

We collect two types of information about you when you visit our Site:  personally identifiable information and non-personal, aggregate information (such as information regarding the pages on our Site that you have visited and your IP address).

(A)  Personally Identifiable Information

“Personally Identifiable Information” is information that identifies you personally, such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, or company name. We collect and store the personal information that you have provided to us. Here are some examples of the ways in which we may collect your personal information on the Site:

When you register on the Site, and in order for you to make use of the functionality of the site, you will be required to give some personal information to generate and maintain your account, such as your first and last name, company name, company operations, company product in information, company address, and company contact details.

We may collect your e-mail address if you contact us with a question.

We may collect your e-mail address if you sign up for an online newsletter.

When you provide feedback regarding the Site, you will be asked for personally identifiable information, such as your name, e-mail address, and organization.  This information will be stored on our Site and used to contact you in response to your feedback, for technical administration of the Site, and to implement improvements to the Site.  

The above list provides an example of the personal information that may be collected by SoutheastAsia.org. From time to time, we may collect personal information from you in other ways that are not described above. If you do not want us to collect your personal information, please do not provide it to us. You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of the personally identifiable information that you submit to us. Inaccurate information will affect the information you receive when using our Site and our ability to contact you as described in this Privacy Policy.

(B) Non-Personally Identifiable Information

“Non-Personally Identifiable Information” can be technical information or it can be demographic information, such as your age, gender, or interests. Even if you do not register with SoutheastAsia.org, we collect non-personally identifiable information about your use of the Site. Non-personally identifiable information does NOT identify you personally. For example, we may conduct research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us upon registration, from our server log files, or from surveys. We do this to better understand and serve you. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis.

We also may collect non-personally identifiable information from you in order to customize your experience, fulfill your requests for information, and improve our services. 

For example, we utilize cookies on the Site. The Internet browser you use has a feature called cookies. This stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to our Site. Our cookies store tracking codes to enable our system to locate information from past visits to the Site, but do not contain information that identifies you personally.  SoutheastAsia.org uses cookies and other technologies to stay in sync with general user-traffic patterns and for the following purposes: 

To keep count of return visits to our site.

To accumulate and report anonymous, aggregate, statistical information on the Site.

To send you information that you have agreed to receive about topics that are of interest to you.

To determine how well each page performs overall based on aggregate user demographics and traffic patterns to such pages.

To determine which feature SoutheastAsia.org’s overall user population prefers best.

We may provide this non-personally identifiable information to third parties. For example, we might inform third parties about the number of users of our Site and the activities they conduct while on the Site. We also may provide trusted partners with general information regarding our users and visitors.

Finally, SoutheastAsia.org may combine any public information you provide in any of the public areas on the Site with non-personally identifiable information to create aggregate data. This information may also be disclosed to third parties. Aggregate data does not contain any information that could be used to contact you or identify you personally.

Use and Disclosure of Personally Identifiable and Non-Personally Identifiable Information

(A) Personally Identifiable Information

We may share or disclose your personal information in the following instances:

To fulfill a service to you. We may use your personally identifiable information to contact you about products that we believe may be of interest to you. We may also use your personally identifiable information to send you newsletters, if requested by you.

To unaffiliated third-party service providers, agents or independent contractors who help us maintain our Site and provide other administrative services to us (including, but not limited to, order processing and fulfillment, providing customer service, maintaining and analyzing data, and sending customer communications on our behalf.

To comply with the law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal process served on us, protect and defend our rights or property or act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of our end users.

To third parties as part of any corporate reorganization process including, but not limited to, mergers, acquisitions, or sales of all or substantially all of our assets.

 To track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers and provide such information to third parties.

To protect against potential fraud, we may verify with third parties the information collected from this Site. In the course of such verification, we may receive personally identifiable information about you from such services. 

To handle any physical or other type of threat made to you or others, to protect property or to defend or assert legal rights.

Except as described in this Privacy Policy or at the time we request the information, we do not otherwise use, share or otherwise disclose your personal information to any third parties.  

(B) Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Non-personally identifiable information is used as described in Section I(B) and in other ways as permitted by applicable laws, including combining non-personally identifiable information with personally identifiable information.

Username and Password

Certain parts of the Site will require you to register and obtain a password in order to enjoy the services offered on the applicable pages of the Site.  When you try to access features of the Site that require registration, you will be prompted to input your username and password information. If you forget your password or username, you can click on the “Forgot Password” link on the login form to obtain your registration information.

SoutheastAsia.org advises those users who do not wish to provide any such data requested by our registration process to refrain from registering with us as SoutheastAsia.org lets you view much of the content without registering. 

Suggestions to SoutheastAsia.org 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any content, business information, ideas, concepts or inventions that you may elect to send to SoutheastAsia.org by e-mail or post anywhere on the Site, including the public areas of the Site. If you want to keep content or business information, ideas, concepts or inventions private or proprietary, do not send them in an e-mail to SoutheastAsia.org or post them on the Site.

Public Areas of the Site

Certain places within the Site, such as forums, blog pages or other public areas, may allow users to post comments or communications that are publicly accessible and non-confidential. Any information shared, including personally identifiable information, in these public areas is not going to be maintained as private and will be accessible to the public.

Whatever information you display on such public forums can be read, copied, collected, or used by other individuals/third parties to send you unsolicited messages. SoutheastAsia.org is not responsible for any information that you choose to disclose in these public areas.

Children Under the Age of 13

Neither SoutheastAsia.org nor any of its services are designed or intended for children under the age of 13. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13.  If a child under the age of 13 submits personal information to SoutheastAsia.org, and SoutheastAsia.org learns that such personal information is the information of a child under the age of 13, we will make every effort to delete the information as soon as possible. 

Links to Third Party Sites

From time to time, SoutheastAsia.org may offer you content through a web site hosted and operated by a third party. In addition, the Site may contain links to other third party web sites operated by companies that are not affiliated with SoutheastAsia.org and that do not have contracts to provide content or services through SoutheastAsia.org. These links may be found in advertisements, referenced within content, or placed beside the names or logos of sponsors. SoutheastAsia.org does not endorse and is not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. If you choose to link to one of these third party web sites, you should review the privacy policy posted on such a web site to understand how that web site collects and uses your personally identifiable information.

Reporting Unsolicited E-mail

SoutheastAsia.org will continue concerted efforts to prevent unsolicited (spam) e-mail from being relayed as SoutheastAsia.org never sends unsolicited or spam e-mail. SoutheastAsia.org considers spam to be violation of privacy and a misuse of the Internet in general. If you receive an unsolicited e-mail with a domain of SoutheastAsia.org’s Site, please inform us immediately so that we can track down the offender and take any actions, legal or as is appropriate, to stop such spam messages.

How SoutheastAsia.org Handles Privacy and Security Internally

SoutheastAsia.org strives to protect your personal information and privacy, but no data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  Consequently, SoutheastAsia.org will not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or share with us online and cannot be responsible for any instances of identity theft, destruction or inadvertent disclosure of your personal information.  Any information you transmit to us is done at your own risk.

We take all reasonable measures to ensure that your personally identifiable information remains as secure as reasonably possible. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access your personally identifiable information. These personnel must abide by our privacy policy.

Here are some of the other security procedures that SoutheastAsia.org uses to protect your privacy:

Requires both a personal username (log-in name) and a password in order for users to access their personally identifiable information.

Uses firewalls to protect information held in our servers.

Utilizes Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption in transmitting personally identifiable information to our servers.

Whatever information is collected and stored with SoutheastAsia.org brings with it special obligations and responsibilities. SoutheastAsia.org will exercise utmost care and precaution to maintain the data’s integrity, security, and privacy. SoutheastAsia.org will not sell or rent out such data. 

Questions & Comments

SoutheastAsia.org encourages you to share any questions or comments you have regarding this Privacy Policy or any other aspects of our Site. SoutheastAsia.org will read and review such messages and attempt to address the questions or concerns contained in them. SoutheastAsia.org may also collect, store or file your comments to improve the SoutheastAsia.org site, or review and discard the information if it is not applicable or relevant to SoutheastAsia.org.  We may be contacted at: admin@SoutheastAsia.org. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Note that SoutheastAsia.org may, from time to time, modify this Privacy Policy to reflect legal, technological, and any other developments. SoutheastAsia.org reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy as necessary. We will indicate the most current date of any change and encourage you to consult our Privacy Policy from time to time. Continued use of SoutheastAsia.org’s web services indicates you accept such changes. SoutheastAsia.org reserves the right to discontinue or add website functionality to support its goals.

Last Updated: January 5, 2010
